{
    "subject": "resource/Barcelona\u2013Cerb\u00e8re_railway",
    "predicate": "property/locale",
    "object": "resource/Catalonia",
    "human_readable": "The Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway is located in Catalonia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9682238101959229,
            "question": "What is the significance of the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway in Catalonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9548307061195374,
            "question": "Where is the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8045207262039185,
            "question": "What type of railway is the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7040926814079285,
            "question": "What region in Spain does the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway run through?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6618142127990723,
            "question": "Is the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway a part of Europe's rail network?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5972778797149658,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks or scenic views along the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5424141883850098,
            "question": "Can you name any cities connected by the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4267053008079529,
            "question": "How long is the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway route?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36081138253211975,
            "question": "Does the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway connect to France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25509369373321533,
            "question": "What time of year would be ideal for a train journey on the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway is located in Catalonia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2887_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway connect to France?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2887_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How long is the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway route?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2887_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any cities connected by the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2887_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2887_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2887_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2887_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2887_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2887_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2887_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2887_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2887_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2887_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2887_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the Barcelona\u2013Cerb\u00e8re railway is a 168-kilometre (104.39 mi) railway line linking Barcelona in Catalonia, Spain to Cerb\u00e8re in France. This information supports the statement that the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway is located in Catalonia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the Barcelona\u2013Cerb\u00e8re railway passes through the Catalan regional cities of Girona and Figueres, which are located in Catalonia, Spain. Therefore, the statement \"The Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway is located in Catalonia\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}